Got to ask you about the Bob the Builder
line, which seems to be a crowd
favorite.
>> I'll put a bullet in Bob the [__]
[music] Builder before they try and kick
us out the building. What about the
children?
>> When you write a line like that, do you
know like, "Okay, that's going to be
like a
>> I didn't even think of it as a big deal.
I was just like, "Bob the Builder
represents it represents someone who
like come knock down these buildings or
gentrifier, something like that. The
next line matters more. You know what
I'm saying?
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> What about the children? When I check a
news channel, I'm now I'm talking about
Palestine and Gaza and all of these
things. I check a news channel, I get a
similar feeling, but still we're going
to make it to heaven, or hell.
>> [music]
>> All of this stuff that's going on around
the world and the kids that are dying.
>> Mhm.
>> We're talking about buildings and what
about the children? I think that's just
like super cool cuz kids watch Bob the
Builder and then we're talking about
true pain and people dying and lives
being lost and